rdasia.com.ph 2012-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Reader's Digest Philippines

**General Statement**

Many Internet users are unaware of how easy it is to give away information about themselves when they navigate the Internet. We, at Reader's Digest Asia Limited, respect and protect the privacy of visitors to our website at URL [http://www.rdasia.com](http://www.rdasia.com/) including the web pages that form a part of this website ("our Website"). Our privacy policy sets out how we use certain types of information that we collect as a result of your visit to our Website.

**Record of visits**

When you visit our Website, our server makes a record of the visits and logs your server Internet protocol address, your domain name, the date and time of visit to our Website, the webpages that you have accessed and documents downloaded, the previous site visited and the type of browser used. This information is used for statistical purposes and no attempt is made to identify users, or their browsing activities, unless we are required by the law to do so.

**Collection of information**

We also collect personally identifiable information such as your e-mail address or other personal details (collectively known as "Personally Identifiable Information") during activities such as purchasing items from our Website, registration for sweepstakes (the "Activities") and contacting our Customer Relationship Department through the Internet or our Website. Please note that this list of the Activities is not exhaustive and we will from time to time increase the range of such activities. However, this privacy policy will still apply to such activities. The Personally Identifiable Information we collect will typically be used by us to offer you special promotional offers and exciting product opportunities through various communication channels from time to time. We may occasionally make your Personally Identifiable Information available to other carefully screened marketers who, we believe, have products of interest to you. Should you not wish to receive these offers, please notify us by e-mail to that effect.

If you are under the age of 21, you are not permitted to participate in the Activities nor will we respond to your queries (whether made through the Internet or our Website). If you wish to participate in the Activities or us to respond to you, you will need to provide us with evidence to our satisfaction that your parent or guardian has consented to your participation in the Activities or to you contacting us.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

From time to time, we may send you offers via various communication channels for our quality products or services that could be of interest to you. And occasionally we may make your name available to other reputable companies whose products or services we believe you may find attractive. If you do not wish to receive such offers, please let us know. Should you like to examine or correct any of your information in our files, please write to our Data Privacy Officer at Reader's Digest, P.O. Box 600, Singapore Post Centre, Singapore 914020. You can also fax to 67491312, or email to [friends@rdasia.com.sg](mailto:friends@rdasia.com.sg)

In an effort to serve you better, it may be necessary for us to share your name, address, or other customer information with Reader's Digest associated companies and with others who provide services essential to our fulfillment and servicing of customers.

**Cookies**

We make use of "cookies" to make our Website perform better. Cookies are small text files that a website will store on your computer to enable it to recognize repeat users. Cookies are not programs that come into a user’s system to damage files. Cookies are used to help us follow the pattern of movements of web users such as which pages on our Website you visit, in what order and how often. By themselves, cookies cannot be used by us to discover your identity? They merely identify your computer to our Website when you visit. Cookies are not used to record any Personal Identifiable Information such as your name, addressor e-mail address. If you are unhappy about having a cookie assigned to you, you can configure your browser to refuse to accept cookies.

**Information by mail**

We appreciate that some people may not wish to submit information via email or the Internet. If you do not wish to submit Personally Identifiable Information to us through our Website or via email, you can write to Customer Relationship Department at: Reader's Digest, P O Box 600, Singapore Post Centre, Singapore 914020 or call us at 6258 1111
